A Guide to the W. W. LaPrade and Brothers Records, 1803-2001 (bulk 1900-1970)
Library of Virginia
- Series I: Chesterfield County Vertical files, 1844-2001 (bulk 1940-1970)., Extent: 7 boxes. (Box 1-7)
  - Subseries 6. Midlothian District., 1 box (1 cu. ft.)
    - Midlothian 2. (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Midlothian 2. (Box 6, Folder 23)
      Bon Air (1818-1932) and Bon Air Presbyterian Church (1994)
    - Midlothian 2. (Box 6, Folder 24)
      Stony Point Reformed Presbyterian Church at Bon Air
    - Midlothian 3. (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Midlothian 4-1. (Box 6, Folder 26)
      Staffordshire
    - Midlothian 4-2. (Box 6, Folder 27)
      Old Gun Estates
    - Midlothian 4-3. (Box 6, Folder 28)
      Holiday Hills
    - Midlothian 5. (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Midlothian 5. (Box 6, Folder 30)
      Bethlehem Baptist Church Robious Crossing
    - Midlothian 5. (Box 6, Folder 31)
      Young Manor
    - Midlothian 6. (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Midlothian 6. (Box 6, Folder 33)
      Samuel H. Guza
    - Midlothian 7. (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Midlothian 7. (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Midlothian 7. (Box 6, Folder 35a)
      Duff's Restaurant
    - Midlothian 7. (Box 6, Folder 36)
      Providence Road, now used as Chesterfield police station
    - Midlothian 7. (Box 6, Folder 37)
      Wezs Radio
    - Midlothian 7-1. (Box 6, Folder 38)
      Shadrock Baylor and adjacent properties
    - Midlothian 7-1. (Box 6, Folder 39)
      E.V. Bossieux
    - Midlothian 7-1. (Box 6, Folder 40)
      Sternheimer Brothers
    - Midlothian 7-3. (Box 6, Folder 41)
      Brighton Green
    - Midlothian 8. (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - Midlothian 8-1. (Box 6, Folder 43)
      Cambridge, Woolfolk property
    - Midlothian 9. (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - Midlothian 9. (Box 6, Folder 45)
      Huguenot Commercial Park
    - Midlothian 9. (Box 6, Folder 46)
      Old Farm Road, Valentine F. Charles and Gladys O. Charles
    - Midlothian 10. (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - Midlothian 10. (Box 6, Folder 48)
      Frick Motor Gallery, Inc.
    - Midlothian 10. (Box 6, Folder 49)
      Johnston-Willis Hospital
    - Midlothian 10. (Box 6, Folder 50)
      Whitten Brothers; Salomonsky; Henshaw Gleason tracts
    - Midlothian 11. (Box 6, Folder 51)
    - Midlothian 12. (Box 6, Folder 52)
    - Midlothian 12-A. (Box 6, Folder 53)
    - Midlothian 13. (Box 6, Folder 54)
    - Midlothian 13. (Box 6, Folder 54a)
      Undecided
    - Midlothian 14. (Box 6, Folder 55)
    - Midlothian 15. (Box 6, Folder 56)
    - Midlothian 15-A. (Box 6, Folder 57)
      Izaak Walton League
    - Midlothian 16. (Box 6, Folder 58)
    - Midlothian 16. (Box 6, Folder 59)
      Mt. Pisgah United Methodist Church
    - Midlothian 16-1. (Box 6, Folder 60)
    - Midlothian 17 (1819-1903). (Box 6, Folder 61)
    - Midlothian 17. (Box 6, Folder 61a)
    - Midlothian 17. (Box 6, Folder 62)
      M.W. Enoch and H.M. Henshaw
    - Midlothian 17. (Box 6, Folder 63)
      Lincoln Savings and Loan
    - Midlothian 17. (Box 6, Folder 64)
      Luck Lane, James Nixon
    - Midlothian 17. (Box 6, Folder 65)
      Mike Mozingo, Avon Estates
    - Midlothian 17. (Box 6, Folder 66)
      Stonehenge
    - Midlothian 18. (Box 6, Folder 67)
    - Midlothian 19. (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Midlothian 19. (Box 7, Folder 2)
      Arch Road Apartments
    - Midlothian 19. (Box 7, Folder 3)
      Aunt Sarah's
    - Midlothian 19-A. (Box 7, Folder 4)
      Scottingham
    - Midlothian 20. (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Midlothian 20. (Box 7, Folder 6)
      Adkins Road
    - Midlothian 20-1. (Box 7, Folder 7)
      Wagstaff
    - Midlothian 20-2. (Box 7, Folder 7a)
      J.H. Condrey
    - Midlothian 21. (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Midlothian 21. (Box 7, Folder 9)
      Genito Road
    - Midlothian 21. (Box 7, Folder 10)
      Southside Speedway
    - Midlothian 22. (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Midlothian 22. (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Midlothian 22. (Box 7, Folder 13)
      Genito Forest
    - Midlothian 23. (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Midlothian 23. (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Midlothian 23. (Box 7, Folder 16)
      Edna Brown
    - Midlothian 23. (Box 7, Folder 17)
      Genito Glen Apartments
    - Midlothian 23. (Box 7, Folder 18)
      James River Equipment Company
    - Midlothian 23. (Box 7, Folder 18a)
      Patron and Harris
    - Midlothian 23-1. (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Midlothian miscellaneous. (Box 7, Folder 20)
      Miscellaneous (1803-1909), and Water supply reservoirs, various properties (1965)
    - Midlothian miscellaneous. (Box 7, Folder 21)
      Hallsboro (1821-1895)
    - Midlothian miscellaneous. (Box 7, Folder 22)
      Tomahawk (1827, nd)
- Series II: Henrico County Vertical files, ca. 1920-1990 (bulk 1940-1970)., Extent: 23 boxes. (Box 8-30)
  This series includes plats and surveys, correspondence and deeds, relating to Henrico County. The more recent files, ca. 1980-1990, also include site plan applications, newspaper clippings, utility, sewer, and topographical maps, memos, soil evaluation reports, and building ordinances relating to the properties.
  - Subseries 1. Brookland District., 4 boxes (4 cu. ft.)
    - Brookland H-16. (Box 8, Folder 1)
      AT & T
    - Brookland H-17. (Box 8, Folder 2)
      Best Products - I-95/Parham Road
    - Brookland H-18. (Box 8, Folder 3)
      Danko's, Quality Inn, Aunt Sarah's, etc.
    - Brookland H-18. (Box 8, Folder 4)
      Virginia Randolph School
    - Brookland H-18. (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Brookland H-18. (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Brookland H-19. (Box 8, Folder 7)
      Brookland Middle School
    - Brookland H-19. (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Brookland H-19. (Box 8, Folder 9)
      Dankos Park
    - Brookland H-19. (Box 8, Folder 10)
      Farm Fresh - Brook Road
    - Brookland H-19. (Box 8, Folder 11)
      Henrico Mental Health Clinic - Woodman Road
    - Brookland H-19. (Box 8, Folder 12)
      Hilliard Road Apartments
    - Brookland H-19. (Box 8, Folder 13)
      Hollybrook II at St. Joseph's Villa
    - Brookland H-19. (Box 8, Folder 14)
      J. Sergeant Reynolds College/Aspen Station
    - Brookland H-19. (Box 8, Folder 15)
      McDonald's - Route 1/Parham Road
    - Brookland H-19. (Box 8, Folder 16)
      Nations Bank - 1714 Lakeside Avenue
    - Brookland H-19. (Box 8, Folder 17)
      Parham Road Medical Center
    - Brookland H-19. (Box 8, Folder 18)
      James Snipes - Mountain Road
    - Brookland H-19. (Box 8, Folder 19)
      St. Joseph's Villa
    - Brookland H-19. (Box 8, Folder 20-22)
      Woodman West Apartments
    - Brookland H-20. (Box 9, Folder 1)
      J. Robert Carlton/Assoc - Azalea/Route 1
    - Brookland H-20. (Box 9, Folder 2-3)
      Colonial Stores - Lakeside Avenue
    - Brookland H-21. (Box 9, Folder 4)
      Robert Wilton - "Shirley"
    - Brookland H-22B. (Box 9, Folder 5)
      Funworks Realty
    - Brookland H-22B. (Box 9, Folder 6-8)
      Loveland Distributing Company - 2290 Dabney Road
    - Brookland H-22B. (Box 9, Folder 9)
      Nola Melton - Dabney Road/Clay Street
    - Brookland H-22D. (Box 9, Folder 10)
      Krispy Kreme Doughnuts - 4910 W. Broad Street
    - Brookland H-22D. (Box 9, Folder 11)
      Meineke Muffler - 5216 W. Broad Street
    - Brookland H-22E. (Box 9, Folder 12)
      CNB - Staples Mill/Bethlehem
    - Brookland H-23. (Box 9, Folder 13)
      7212 Bethlehem Road
    - Brookland H-23. (Box 9, Folder 14)
      Joseph W. Bliley Funeral Home
    - Brookland H-23. (Box 9, Folder 15)
      Boudar Gardens
    - Brookland H-23. (Box 9, Folder 16)
      Brookfield
    - Brookland H-23. (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Brookland H-23. (Box 9, Folder 17a)
    - Brookland H-23. (Box 9, Folder 18)
      Brookfield Parking Lot - Hardwicke
    - Brookland H-23. (Box 9, Folder 19)
      Brookfield - Richmond Corporation
    - Brookland H-23. (Box 9, Folder 20-22)
      Crestar Bank
    - Brookland H-23. (Box 9, Folder 23)
      James Fox and Sons - Wistar Road Warehouse
    - Brookland H-23. (Box 9, Folder 24)
      Grandy's Restaurant - Broad/Calloway
    - Brookland H-23. (Box 9, Folder 25)
      Hartford I - Henrico Corporate Center
    - Brookland H-23. (Box 9, Folder 26)
      Hartford II
    - Brookland H-23. (Box 9, Folder 27)
      Hermitage High School
    - Brookland H-23. (Box 9, Folder 28)
      Hungary Springs Office Building
    - Brookland H-23. (Box 9, Folder 29)
      Hungary Springs Office Park
    - Brookland H-23. (Box 9, Folder 30-31)
      K-Mart - Glenside Drive/Three Chopt
    - Brookland H-23. (Box 10, Folder 1)
      Laurel Village Apartments
    - Brookland H-23. (Box 10, Folder 2)
      Mike Mozingo
    - Brookland H-23. (Box 10, Folder 3)
      Virginia Trust Company - Parham Road/Hungary Springs Road
    - Brookland H-23. (Box 10, Folder 4)
      Vistas at Brookfield
    - Brookland H-23. (Box 10, Folder 5)
      Walkenhut Estates
    - Brookland H-23. (Box 10, Folder 6)
      Willis/Staples Mill Road - 92-B2-23
    - Brookland H-23. (Box 10, Folder 7-8)
      Wistar Center - Staples Mill Road
    - Brookland H-24. (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Brookland H-24. (Box 10, Folder 10)
      RF/P Park - Mountain Road
    - Brookland H-24. (Box 10, Folder 11)
      RF/P Railroad Property - Richmond Newspapers, Inc.
    - Brookland HB-16. (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Brookland HB-17. (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Brookland HB-17-2. (Box 10, Folder 14)
      Wildwood
    - Brookland HB-17-3. (Box 10, Folder 15)
      Carrington
    - Brookland HB-18. (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Brookland HB-18-1. (Box 10, Folder 17)
      Woodcliff
    - Brookland HB-19. (Box 10, Folder 18)
      Robert Ball, Sr. - Parham Road/North Run
    - Brookland HB-19. (Box 10, Folder 19)
      Henrico County Public Schools
    - Brookland HB-19. (Box 10, Folder 20)
      North Run Hills/North Run Terrace
    - Brookland HB-19. (Box 10, Folder 21)
      Oakmont
    - Brookland HB-19. (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Brookland HB-19-1. (Box 10, Folder 23)
      Tracings: Putney Place, Brookland Gardens, Green Acres, Richmond Land Corps., Oakmont Hills
    - Brookland HB-19-2. (Box 10, Folder 24)
      Hermitage West
    - Brookland HB-20. (Box 10, Folder 25)
      Pure Oil Company - Hilliard Road/Lakeside Avenue and Colonial Stores Incorporated
    - Brookland HB-20. (Box 10, Folder 26)
      Whitaker/Harmon Properties
    - Brookland HB-20-1. (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Brookland HB-20-2. (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Brookland HB-21. (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Brookland HB-22. (Box 11, Folder 4)
      Westbourne - Section F
    - Brookland HB-22-1. (Box 11, Folder 5)
      Westbourne - Section E and Hampstead Apartments
    - Brookland HB-22-3. (Box 11, Folder 6)
      Westbourne - Section C and D
    - Brookland HB-22-4. (Box 11, Folder 7)
      Westbourne - Section A and B
    - Brookland HB-22-4. (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Brookland HB-22-A. (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Brookland HB-22-B. (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Brookland HB-22-C. (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Brookland HB-22-C. (Box 11, Folder 12)
      Myrtle M. Holland
    - Brookland HB-22-D. (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Brookland HB-22-E. (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Brookland HB-22-F. (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Brookland HB-22-G. (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Brookland HB-22-H. (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Brookland HB-23. (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Brookland HB-23. (Box 11, Folder 19)
      C & P Telephone - Bell Atlantic - Hungary Springs Road
    - Brookland HB-23-1. (Box 11, Folder 20)
      Tuscon Heights
    - Brookland HB-23-2. (Box 11, Folder 21)
      Greendale Forest and Greendale Manor
    - Brookland HB-23-2. (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Brookland HB-23-3. (Box 11, Folder 23)
      Woodlawn Farms
    - Brookland HB-23-4. (Box 11, Folder 24)
      Huntington - Ralph May
    - Brookland HB-23-4. (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Brookland Misc. (Box 12, Folder 1)
      Brautigan Heights
    - Brookland Misc. (Box 12, Folder 2)
      Citi Wide Decorators, Inc., Laburnum Ave.
    - Brookland Misc. (Box 12, Folder 3)
      Consolidated Sales
    - Brookland Misc. (Box 12, Folder 4)
      Dr. Dolsey dentist office
    - Brookland Misc. (Box 12, Folder 5)
      Gulf Oil, I-95 and Brook Rd.
    - Brookland Misc. (Box 12, Folder 6)
      Harold Lingerfelt, Strawberry Hill
    - Brookland Misc. (Box 12, Folder 7)
      Henrico County storm sewer, Projects 4 and 4a, Rocky Branch and Cattail Branch
    - Brookland Misc. (Box 12, Folder 8)
      Henrico County storm sewer, Project 10, Greendall Forest
    - Brookland Misc. (Box 12, Folder 9)
      Hyatt House addition, Brookfield
    - Brookland Misc. (Box 12, Folder 10)
      Huntington, Sewage pumping station, auxiliary power
    - Brookland Misc. (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Brookland Misc. (Box 12, Folder 12)
      Kmart, Glenside and Broad
    - Brookland Misc. (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Brookland Misc. (Box 12, Folder 14)
      Lawyer's Title Insurance Building
    - Brookland Misc. (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Brookland Misc. (Box 12, Folder 16)
      Longdale School, Hardwicke
    - Brookland Misc. (Box 12, Folder 17)
      Talley and Flanary Warehouse, Hardwicke
    - Brookland Misc. (Box 13)
  - Subseries 2. Fairfield District., 4 boxes (4 cu. ft.)
    - Fairfield H-10B. (Box 13, Folder 1)
      Alex Armour Property
    - Fairfield H-10B. (Box 13, Folder 2)
      Louis Goldstein Property
    - Fairfield H-10B. (Box 13, Folder 3)
      Hidden Creek Park
    - Fairfield H-10B. (Box 13, Folder 4)
      Laburnum Avenue Library
    - Fairfield H-10B. (Box 13, Folder 5)
      Signet Bank Parking Lot - Mechanicsville Turnpike/Neale Street
    - Fairfield H-10-4. (Box 13, Folder 6)
      Central Gardens - Work Maps
    - Fairfield H-11. (Box 13, Folder 7)
      Charles Goodell - Carter Sand and Gravel
    - Fairfield H-11. (Box 13, Folder 8)
      Goodell to Liesfeld - Old Carter Sand and Gravel Site
    - Fairfield H-11. (Box 13, Folder 9-11)
      Jarrett Apartments
    - Fairfield H-11. (Box 13, Folder 12-13)
      Jarrett Apartments - Offsite Sewer
    - Fairfield H-12. (Box 13, Folder 14)
      Raymond and Beatrice Rudolph - 5510 Jefferson Street - Highland Springs
    - Fairfield H-16. (Box 13, Folder 15)
      3703 Carolina Avenue
    - Fairfield H-16. (Box 13, Folder 16-19)
      Forest Lawn Cemetery
    - Fairfield H-16. (Box 13, Folder 20)
      Wilmer Avenue
    - Fairfield H-17. (Box 13, Folder 21)
      Bluff Springs
    - Fairfield H-17. (Box 13, Folder 22)
      Level 3 Communications LLC
    - Fairfield H-17. (Box 13, Folder 23)
      North Park Library - Parham/Franconia
    - Fairfield H-17. (Box 13, Folder 24)
      Virginia Natural Gas - Route 301
    - Fairfield H-20. (Box 13, Folder 25)
      Communication Workers of America - Lakeside Avenue
    - Fairfield H-20. (Box 13, Folder 26)
      Lakeside Moose - Hilliard Road/North Run
    - Fairfield HF-10-A. (Box 14, Folder 1)
      Montezuma Gardens, Brentwood, Knowles Acres, Martin's Annex
    - Fairfield HF-10-B. (Box 14, Folder 2)
      East View Nursing Home
    - Fairfield HF-10-B. (Box 14, Folder 3)
      Fairfield Development Company
    - Fairfield HF-10-B. (Box 14, Folder 4)
      Roosevelt Park
    - Fairfield HF-10-B. (Box 14, Folder 5)
      Maplewood Farms
    - Fairfield HF-10-B. (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Fairfield HF-10-B. (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Fairfield HF-10-B. (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Fairfield HF-10-2. (Box 14, Folder 9)
      Oak Hill Subdivision
    - Fairfield HF-10-3. (Box 14, Folder 10)
      Wilhaven
    - Fairfield HF-10-4. (Box 14, Folder 11)
      Central Gardens
    - Fairfield HF-10-4. (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Fairfield HF-11. (Box 14, Folder 13)
      American Oil Company
    - Fairfield HF-11. (Box 14, Folder 14)
      Robinwood, Garden City, Montrose Terrace, Martin's Manor
    - Fairfield HF-11-2. (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Fairfield HF-11-3. (Box 14, Folder 16)
      Eastover Gardens
    - Fairfield HF-11-4. (Box 14, Folder 17)
      King's Hill
    - Fairfield HF-11-5. (Box 14, Folder 18)
      Hechler Village Sections 1-8
    - Fairfield HF-11-5. (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Fairfield HF-11-5. (Box 14, Folder 20)
      Hechler Village Sections 9, 10, 12
    - Fairfield HF-11-5. (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Fairfield HF-11-5. (Box 15, Folder 1-5)
      Hechler Village Work Maps
    - Fairfield HF-11-6. (Box 15, Folder 6)
      Laundale Farms Mortgage Surveys
    - Fairfield HF-12-1. (Box 15, Folder 7)
      Confederate Hills, Confederate Terrace
    - Fairfield HF-12-2. (Box 15, Folder 8)
      Highland Springs Elementary School
    - Fairfield HF-12-2. (Box 15, Folder 9)
      Tucker Acres
    - Fairfield HF-12-3. (Box 15, Folder 10)
      Highland Springs
    - Fairfield HF-13. (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Fairfield HF-13. (Box 15, Folder 12)
      Safeway Stores, Wingwood Park
    - Fairfield HF-13-3. (Box 15, Folder 13)
      O'Grady Manor
    - Fairfield HF-14. (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Fairfield HF-15. (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Fairfield Misc. (Box 15, Folder 16-18)
      G/H Sewer Project "C" Deeds and Maps Part I and II
    - Fairfield Misc. (Box 16, Folder 1-3)
      G/H Sewer Project "C" Deeds and Maps Part III
    - Fairfield Misc. (Box 16, Folder 4)
      King and Queen Square Apartments Sewer
    - Fairfield Misc. (Box 16, Folder 5)
      Mobil Oil
    - Fairfield Misc. (Box 16, Folder 6)
      STP - Laburnum/I-64 - Mobil Oil
    - Fairfield Misc. (Box 16, Folder 7)
      Virginia Federal Savings and Loan
  - Subseries 3. Three Chopt District., 2 boxes (2 cu. ft.)
    - Three Chopt H-22-D. (Box 17, Folder 1)
      Broadly
    - Three Chopt H-22-D. (Box 17, Folder 2)
      Freelich Theatre
    - Three Chopt H-22-F. (Box 17, Folder 3)
      Rustler Steak House - Falmouth/Broad
    - Three Chopt H-23. (Box 17, Folder 4)
      A.G. Bolton Tract
    - Three Chopt H-23. (Box 17, Folder 5)
      Brookfield Commons - 6600 W. Broad Street
    - Three Chopt H-23. (Box 17, Folder 6)
      Colyer Center
    - Three Chopt H-23. (Box 17, Folder 7)
      Farm Fresh - Store #365
    - Three Chopt H-23. (Box 17, Folder 8)
      Pruitt Property - Broad/Wistar
    - Three Chopt H-23. (Box 17, Folder 9-12)
      West Tower Place Shopping Center
    - Three Chopt H-28. (Box 17, Folder 13)
      Amoco - Broad/Libbie
    - Three Chopt H-28. (Box 17, Folder 14)
      Bill's Barbecue - Broad Street
    - Three Chopt H-28. (Box 17, Folder 15)
      St. Mary's Hospital
    - Three Chopt H-28. (Box 17, Folder 16)
      Westview Manor, Monument Heights
    - Three Chopt H-28-C. (Box 17, Folder 17)
      Shenandoah Place
    - Three Chopt H-30-C. (Box 17, Folder 18)
      Douglas Freeman High School
    - Three Chopt H-32-A. (Box 17, Folder 19)
      Henrico Doctors Hospital
    - Three Chopt H-32-A. (Box 17, Folder 20)
      Henrico Professional Condominiums
    - Three Chopt H-32-A. (Box 17, Folder 21)
      Cheswick Farm
    - Three Chopt H-32-A. (Box 17, Folder 22)
      Westbury Estates, Michael Road
    - Three Chopt H-32-A. (Box 17, Folder 23)
      Robertshaw Controls Co. - Glenside Drive
    - Three Chopt H-32-C. (Box 17, Folder 24)
      Maypar Office Park
    - Three Chopt H-32-C. (Box 17, Folder 25)
      Women's Bank
    - Three Chopt H-32-D. (Box 17, Folder 26-27)
      Commerce Center - 2812 Emerywood Parkway
    - Three Chopt H-32-D. (Box 17, Folder 28)
      Commerce Center - F. G. Pruitt
    - Three Chopt H-32-D. (Box 17, Folder 29-33)
      Commerce Center - Pruitt's
    - Three Chopt H-32-D. (Box 17, Folder 34)
    - Three Chopt H-35-A. (Box 18, Folder 1)
      Tracings
    - Three Chopt H-35-C. (Box 18, Folder 2-5)
      Pouncy Tract Park
    - Three Chopt H-35-C. (Box 18, Folder 6)
      W. Griffin Purcell Estate
    - Three Chopt H-35-2. (Box 18, Folder 7)
      Chelsea Square Apartments
    - Three Chopt Misc. (Box 18, Folder 8)
      Brookfield - Condominium Sales Office
    - Three Chopt Misc. (Box 18, Folder 9)
      Brookfield - Office Building #2
    - Three Chopt Misc. (Box 18, Folder 10)
      Continental Building
    - Three Chopt Misc. (Box 18, Folder 11)
      General Motors - Argonaut Building - Hardwicke
    - Three Chopt Misc. (Box 18, Folder 12-13)
      Infilco-Degremont
  - Subseries 4. Tuckahoe District., 7 boxes (7 cu. ft.)
    - Tuckahoe H-26. (Box 19, Folder 1)
      5999 River Road - Salomonsky to Sauer - 6/99
    - Tuckahoe H-26. (Box 19, Folder 2)
      6500 Westham Station Road
    - Tuckahoe H-26. (Box 19, Folder 3)
      Jane-Mark Associates POD 125-87/Jane Lynne Sternheimer
    - Tuckahoe H-28-8. (Box 19, Folder 4)
      Meals on Wheels - 1600 Willow Lawn Drive
    - Tuckahoe H-30-B. (Box 19, Folder 5)
      8501 Patterson Avenue
    - Tuckahoe H-30-B. (Box 19, Folder 6)
      Virginia Trust Company - Forest/Patterson
    - Tuckahoe H-31. (Box 19, Folder 7)
      Sleepy Hollow - Lot 37
    - Tuckahoe H-31-A. (Box 19, Folder 8)
      Dr. Richard Bartley - Quioccasin Road
    - Tuckahoe H-31-A. (Box 19, Folder 9)
      Beth Sholom Elderly Home - Lauderdale/Gayton
    - Tuckahoe H-31-A. (Box 19, Folder 10)
      Cardinal Savings and Loan - Parham Road
    - Tuckahoe H-31-A. (Box 19, Folder 11)
      Crown Service Station - Patterson/Quail Lane
    - Tuckahoe H-31-A. (Box 19, Folder 12)
      Helen Konstantinakos - 1106 Parham Road
    - Tuckahoe H-31-A. (Box 19, Folder 13)
      Lauderdale to Gayton Between Beth Sholom Home/Queens Point Subdivision
    - Tuckahoe H-31-A. (Box 19, Folder 14)
      George Layne - Gayton/Ryandale
    - Tuckahoe H-31-A. (Box 19, Folder 15)
      Mobil Oil - Patterson/Westbriar
    - Tuckahoe H-31-B. (Box 19, Folder 16)
      Brandon West - Jerome Gumenick
    - Tuckahoe H-31-B. (Box 19, Folder 17)
      Henrico Fire Station 17 - Gaskins/River Road
    - Tuckahoe H-31-C. (Box 19, Folder 18)
      Harry Grandis - River/Herndon Roads
    - Tuckahoe H-31-C. (Box 19, Folder 19)
      Roslyn - 8727 River Road
    - Tuckahoe H-32-D. (Box 19, Folder 20)
      Mini-Warehouses - Jerry Levey - Broad Street Road
    - Tuckahoe H-32-D. (Box 19, Folder 21)
      Pine Dell Shopping Center - Milton Perel
    - Tuckahoe H-35. (Box 19, Folder 22)
      Crown Grant - Wynmoor
    - Tuckahoe H-35. (Box 19, Folder 23-27)
      Mills Godwin High School
    - Tuckahoe H-35. (Box 19, Folder 28)
      Bernard Nash - Twin Hickory Stables
    - Tuckahoe H-35. (Box 19, Folder 29-30)
      Oak Ridge Subdivision
    - Tuckahoe H-35. (Box 19, Folder 31)
      University Park (Walter Regirer)
    - Tuckahoe H-35. (Box 19, Folder 32-33)
      Whitaker Woods
    - Tuckahoe H-35. (Box 20, Folder 1-4)
    - Tuckahoe H-35-A. (Box 20, Folder 5)
      3201/05 Skipwith Road
    - Tuckahoe H-35-A. (Box 20, Folder 6)
      9001 Three Chopt Road - Tom Harris
    - Tuckahoe H-35-A. (Box 20, Folder 7)
      Best Products - Quioccasin Road
    - Tuckahoe H-35-A. (Box 20, Folder 8)
      Crown Central - Ridgefield/Flintwood (7/89)
    - Tuckahoe H-35-A. (Box 20, Folder 9)
      Tuckahoe Library - Starling Drive
    - Tuckahoe H-35-B. (Box 20, Folder 10)
      Discover Methodist Church
    - Tuckahoe H-35-C. (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Tuckahoe H-35-D. (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Tuckahoe HT-26. (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Tuckahoe HT-28. (Box 20, Folder 14)
      Duntreath
    - Tuckahoe HT-28-1. (Box 20, Folder 15)
      Westhaven - Section B
    - Tuckahoe HT-28-2. (Box 20, Folder 16)
      Westhaven
    - Tuckahoe HT-28-3. (Box 20, Folder 17)
      Monument Hills
    - Tuckahoe HT-28-4. (Box 20, Folder 18-19)
      Westwood Terrace
    - Tuckahoe HT-28-7-1. (Box 20, Folder 20)
      North Willow Lawn Section A
    - Tuckahoe HT-28-8. (Box 20, Folder 21)
      North Willow Lawn Section B and Shopping Center
    - Tuckahoe HT-28-8. (Box 20, Folder 22)
      Willow Lawn Bridges (Jordan's Branch)
    - Tuckahoe HT-28-8. (Box 20, Folder 23)
      5100 Monument Avenue
    - Tuckahoe HT-28-9. (Box 20, Folder 24)
      Belle Air
    - Tuckahoe HT-28-A. (Box 20, Folder 25)
      Westwood/Westwood Home Sites/Westwood Manor
    - Tuckahoe HT-30. (Box 20, Folder 26)
      Westham and Westham Ridge